[
    {
        "front": "にちようび",
        "back": "日曜日 \nSunday",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "にほん",
        "back": "日本 \nJapan",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "つき",
        "back": "月 \nThe moon",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "げつようび",
        "back": "月曜日 \nMonday",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちがつ",
        "back": "一月 \nJanuary",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんげつ",
        "back": "今月 \nThis month",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひ",
        "back": "火 \nFire",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "かようび",
        "back": "火曜日 \nTuesday",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふじさん",
        "back": "ふじ山 \nMt.fuji",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "かわ",
        "back": "川 \nRiver",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "やまかわ さん",
        "back": "山川さん \nMr./Ms Yamakawa",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "たんぼ",
        "back": "田 \nRice Field",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "やまだ さん",
        "back": "山田さん \nMr./Ms Yamada",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "みず",
        "back": "水 \nWater",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "すいようび",
        "back": "水曜日 \nWednesday",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "き",
        "back": "木 \ntree",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "もくようび",
        "back": "木曜日 \nThursday",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "おかね",
        "back": "お金 \nMoney",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きん",
        "back": "金 \nGold",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "きんようび",
        "back": "金曜日 \nFriday",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "つち",
        "back": "土 \nSiol, earth",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "どようび",
        "back": "土曜日 \nSaturday",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    },
    {
        "front": "ひ",
        "back": "日 \nThe sun",
        "chapter": "N5 K1"
    }
]